Gayniggers from Outer Space is a comedy, science
fiction film directed by Morten Lindberg.
Extraterrestrial beings travel the galaxy to free men "oppressed" by
females to make way for an entirely-homosexual society.
Sgt. Shaved Balls, played by Gbatokai Dakinah.
Capt. B. Dick, played by Sammy Salomon.
ArmInAss, played by Coco C.P. Dalbert.
Mr. Schwul, played by Konrad Fields.
Narrator (voice), played by Bob Rockwell.
Sgt. Shaved Balls (voice), played by Rob Pederson.
Gayniggers from Outer Space is a 1992 Danish English-language satirical science
fiction short film, directed by Danish performance artist Morten Lindberg.
The film is a parody of the science fiction and blaxploitation genres.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, space travel, satire, parody, alien.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.